Guide to the Michael Francis Blake photographs, 1912-1934 RL.00119
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original photographs, circa 1912-1934; .25 Linear Feet 1 box 118 prints
  - Studio photograph, seated infant propped up on a chair, unidentified, 1933 June 19, 3.5 x 5.5. Writing on photograph: "June Thursday 1933 Pass - 3 months old". Embossed with Blake's studio address. Same photograph as MFB013. (Box 1, Print MFB096)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, identified as E. H. Coit, circa 1912, 3.25 x 4.25. E.H. Coit is listed as a "mulatto preacher" born about 1860 in the 1910 Federal census. He may have been about 50 in this photograph. (Box 1, Print MFB097)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, identified as E. H. Coit, circa 1912, 3.25 x 4.25. E.H. Coit is listed as a "mulatto preacher" born about 1860 in the 1910 Federal census. He may have been about 50 in this photograph. Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1, Print MFB098)
  - Studio photograph, two seated adult females, identified as Evelyn Read and Agnes Read, circa 1926-1934, 3.5 x 5.5. Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1, Print MFB099)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult male, unidentified, undated, 3.75 x 5.5 (Box 1, Print MFB100)
  - Studio photograph, adult female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, 3.5 x 5.5. Has Blake's 384 W. Sumter address. (Box 1, Print MFB101)
  - Studio photograph, adult female dressed in a man's suit, identified as Mary Buckingham Brown, circa 1926-1934, 3.5 x 5.5. Negative on file. (Box 1, Print MFB102)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female, unidentified, before 1918, 3.5 x 5.5. Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake, View Photographer, 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." Date of photograph is derived from address, which changed to 384 when the street was renumbered in 1918. (Box 1, Print MFB103)
  - Studio photograph, adult female, unidentified, after 1918, 3.5 x 5.5. Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake, Night and Day Photographer, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1, Print MFB104)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult female, identified as Pauline Buckingham, circa 1918-1922, 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1, Print MFB105)
  - Studio photograph, elderly female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1, Print MFB106)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, circa 1926-1934, 3.5 x 5.5. Embossed with Blake's studio address at 384 W. Sumter Street. (Box 1, Print MFB107)
  - Studio photograph, standing male child next to an infant seated on a chair, unidentified, circa 1926-1939, 3.5 x 5.5. Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1, Print MFB108)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female dressed in bridal wear, unidentified, circa 1926-1934, 3.5 x 5.5. Embossed with Blake's studio address at 384 W. Sumter Street. (Box 1, Print MFB109)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1, Print MFB110)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female, unidentified, undated, not taken by Blake, 4.25 x 6.25. Mounted photograph is identified as produced by William D. Clarke, a white photographer in Charleston, S.C. (Box 1, Print MFB111)
  - Snapshot, adult male standing by a house, unidentified, undated, 4 x 6. Mounted snapshot. (Box 1, Print MFB112)
  - Studio photograph, head shot of adult female, unidentified, before 1918, 5 x 7 (mount size). Small circular photograph, approximately 1 inch, mounted within larger embossed mount with oval frame. Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake, View Photographer, 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1, Print MFB113)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, after 1918, 5 x 7 (mount size). Mounted oval portrait. Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake, Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1, Print MFB114)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult male between two boys holding rifles and a younger male child in front of them, unidentified, before 1918, 5 x 7 (mount size). Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1, Print MFB115)
  - Snapshot, elderly man seated in a doorway holding a cane, unidentified, undated, 5 x 7 (mount size). Mounted photograph. (Box 1, Print MFB116)
  - Group portrait, uniformed nurses, possibly a class picture at the Hospital and Training School for Nurses, Charleston, S.C., unidentified, undated, 5 x 7 (Box 1, Print MFB117)
    Mounted photograph, stamped with Blake's studio address: "M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." Possibly an albumen print.
  - Portrait, probably out of doors, older male, standing, identified as Silas Abrams, Newberry, S.C., 1920s; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 inches. Identified by donor of photograph. This print was a later addition and has not been digitized. (Box 1, Print MFB118)
- Modern reference prints set (preferred for use access), .25 Linear Feet 1 box 117 copy prints
  These copy prints were produced by library staff; most are black-and-white but some are color reproductions of Blake's black-and-white prints.
  - Reference prints (Box 2)
- Photograph album (photographs have been removed), .5 Linear Feet 1 box 1 volume
  Photograph album (empty) originally housing most of the photographs in this collection. The album title reads "Photographs of members."
  - Album (Box 3)